你把内脏都放盘子里了吗
You put the giblets in a pan?
是的 主厨
Yes, chef.
谢谢 一个名叫副厨的男孩
Thanks, a boy named sous...chef.
我不懂什么意思 但我信你的梗
I don't get it, but I trust you.
好了 菲利普
All right, Philip,
把翅尖塞到火鸡肚子下面
tuck the wing tips under the body of the bird
然后放到烤盘上
and place in a roasting pan.
遵命 我的女神
As you wish, my crumpet.
今年的感恩节晚宴由我掌勺
I am cooking Thanksgiving dinner this year.
让克莱尔信赖我的厨艺真的不容易
Huge step for Claire to trust me with this.
但我有帮手 就是这个新应用
But I have help -- this new app.
国际知名的大厨奈洁拉·劳森
It's, uh, international super chef Nigella Lawson.
我还可以编入我的名字
I can even program my name,
就好像她站在我旁边
so it's like she's right here
用她性感的英式嗓音一步步指导我
guiding my every move with that sultry British voice.
我上周在车里听到她的
I listened to her meringue instructions
蛋白酥皮指南
in the car last week.
各种搅拌[鞭打]
There was so much
害我不得不在路边停下车
whipping and beating I had to pull over.
-进展如何 -很顺利
- How's it going in here? - Great.
你好好享受这个感恩节吧 终于不用
You just take advantage of your first Thanksgiving
在热滚滚的烤炉边汗流浃背
not sweating over a hot stove
最后坐下来吃晚餐时 一身油腻
and having to sit down to dinner
脾气暴躁又筋疲力尽
all gross and grumpy and exhausted.
是啊 今年你终于可以有一份好心情了
Yeah, this year, you can finally be in a good mood.
听你们这番话之前 我确实心情很好
Well, I was until this little riff.
我妈和杰从墨西哥发来了感恩节问候
Mom and Jay sent a Thanksgiving greeting from Mexico.
我都不知道墨西哥也过感恩节
I didn't even know Mexico had Thanksgiving.
就是 我刚才也这么说来着
I know. I said the same thing.
天啊 我们会很想念艾丽克斯的
God, we're really gonna miss Alex.
我还是不理解你为什么要放弃免费旅行
I still don't get why you passed up a free trip.
因为他们得跟23个哥伦比亚人见面
Because they're meeting 23 Colombians
他们管我妈叫"安静的美女子"
who call my mom "La Tranquila" -- the quiet one.
你们好啊 我的家人们
Hola, familia!
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving!
祝你明天生日快乐 卢克
Happy birthday tomorrow, Luke!
卢克 我们没忘记你哦
Yeah, Luke, we didn't forget about you.
我们在墨西哥给你买了个超棒的礼物
We got you a great present here in Mexico.
回去后见咯
See you when we get back.
拜拜 拜拜
Bye! Bye-bye!
再见
See you soon!
卡
And cut.
我想他们会信的
Well, I think we sold that.
哥伦比亚之旅取消了
The Colombians' trip got canceled
因为当地机场跑道发生了泥石流
because a mudslide took out the runway at the local airport.
那里都是用土建起来的
That thing's made of dirt.
你确定不是只是下雨而已吗
Are we sure it didn't just rain?
所以我们根本没走成
So we never left,
我们本来要去菲尔和克莱尔家的 但是
and we could have gone to Phil and Claire's, but...
我们决定自己在家享受
We decided to enjoy our own quiet,
安宁轻松的节日晚宴 不让任何人知道
stress-free holiday dinner at home with no one the wiser.
我们要享受牛排假日
We're having a little steak-cation,
但是吃的是火鸡 不是牛排
only with turkey instead of the steak.
是留宅假日[Stay和Steak音似]
Stay-cation.
-我说的什么 -牛排假日
- What did I say? - "Steak-cation."
是留宅假日
It's stay-cation.
你想用一堂英语课
Oh, so, this is how you want to start
来开启安宁轻松的晚餐吗
the quiet, stress-free dinner, with an English lesson?
他们管她叫"安静的美女子"
They call her "La Tranquila."
我们一定要记得把这个背包还给莉莉
We really need to remember to return this backpack to Lily.
亲爱的 别忘了
Oh, and, honey,
米奇尔不喜欢吃葡萄干
don't forget Mitchell hates raisins.
所以你填火鸡的时候 一点都不能
So when you're making the stuffing, you can't put any --
我知道让你移交管辖权很难
I know how hard it is for you to hand over the reins,
但你得相信我
but you have got to trust me.
我相信你
I do trust you.
只是这些小细节很容易忘嘛
It's just easy to forget the little things.
我什么也不会忘的
I'm not going to forget anything.
走吧
Now go.
你俩快去一趟杂货店
You two need to run to the grocery store.
我忘记买绿豆 番薯和蔓越莓酱了
I forgot green beans, yams, and cranberry sauce.
婴儿床里藏着什么[偷偷摸摸]
What's in the crib?
什么偷偷摸摸 你才偷偷摸摸
What crib? You're a crib.
你不是应该在学习嘛
Shouldn't you be studying?
期中考都结束了
Well, I'm done with my midterms.
大学申请论文也写完了
I finished my college essay.
我正打算出去骑自行车
And I was just about to go on a bike ride.
你怎么一副犯了错的样子
Why are you acting so guilty?
你才犯了错
You're guilty.
我是怎么成为优秀辩手的
How did I ever get to be a champion debater?
是备用火鸡啦
It is a backup turkey.
我怕你爸爸做得不好吃才买的
I bought it in case your father's doesn't work out,
我希望他做得好吃
which I hope it does.
但万一不好吃
But if it doesn't,
这只可以让他免于难堪
this could save him a lot of embarrassment.
请别告诉他
Please don't tell him.
如果他以为我不信任他 会气死的
He would die if he thought I didn't trust him.
有意思
Interesting.
我很快都要去上大学了
I mean, I'm going off to college soon.
你却突然间
All of a sudden,
在我的旧婴儿床里放热乎的东西
you're keeping something warm in my old crib.
来吧 亲爱的 你会更喜欢这个
Here you go, sweetie. You'll like this better.
天啊 你开玩笑呢吗
Oh, my gosh. You got to be kidding me.
别再这样了
Not this again.
什么 她说煎蛋太水了
What? She said her eggs were watery,
所以我给她做了华夫饼
so I made her a waffle.
别小题大做
Please don't make a thing out of it.
我见过你把吃的退回去
I've seen you send food back.
还记得迈阿密那次吗
Remember that time in Miami?
首先 这里不是饭店
Okay, first of all, this isn't a restaurant.
其次 那是因为那份浓汤里有一颗牙
Secondly, my bisque had a tooth in it.
是贝壳
It was a shell.
那是实心的
There was a filling in it.
我不想吃华夫饼
Ugh, I don't feel like waffles.
能不能帮我弄麦片
Can you make me cereal?
-当然 -坚决不行
- Sure. - Absolutely not.
绝对不行 莉莉
Absolutely not, Lily.
把华夫饼吃完
You are gonna finish that waffle,
不然就什么都没得吃
or you're not gonna have breakfast.
那我边看电视边吃总可以吧
Can I at least eat it in front of the TV?
-可以 -不行
- Yes. - No.
谢谢爸爸
Thanks, daddy.
坏爸爸
Mean daddy.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
她每次想要什么你都给 我成了坏爸爸
You give in to her every whim, and I'm mean daddy.
-才没有 -是吗
- That's not true. - Isn't it?
那这是什么
What's this?
这就是我们在她眼里的样子
This is how she sees us.
我是个尖叫的魔鬼
I'm a screaming demon,
你就是快乐小天使
and you're just a-smilin' and a-bakin'.
顺便说下
And, incidentally,
真有必要把这贴冰箱上吗
do we really think this is refrigerator-worthy?
昨天你让她整理房间后她贴上去的
She put it up yesterday after you made her clean her room.
而你给她做了布朗尼蛋糕
And after you made her brownies.
你要是还不对她严一点
She is gonna turn into a willful, fat little girl
她会变成一个任性的小胖子的
unless you start getting tough with her,
现在你是她的小伙伴
because right now you're her pal,
我就是拿着叉子的妖受
and I'm just the pitchfork-wielding she-devil.
我跟画里对上了 是吧
It lined up, didn't it?
是啊 你拿着叉子简直大亮
Yeah, we really got lucky with you holding that fork.
长话短说
Long story short.
要是用倒的 就是蔓越莓酱
If you pour it, it's cranberry sauce.
要是用切的 不好意思
But I'm sorry, if you slice it,
就成蔓越莓果冻了
it's cranberry jelly.
我已经踩足了油门了
I'm literally driving as fast as this car can go.
你袖子里那个是袜子吗
Is that a sock in your sleeve?
我今早在你家洗衣服
I did laundry at your house this morning,
可你们没有除静电纸
and you have no dryer sheets.
我喜欢住在你们家
I like staying with you,
不过这就跟野营一样
but it's basically camping.
对不起
I'm -- I'm so sorry!
我什么也没感觉到
I didn't feel anything.
我是说 我当然有感觉到
I mean, of -- of course I felt something,
你显然很有料 我是说
and you do have them -- I mean --
你怎么不按喇叭
Why didn't you honk?!
那样不就更糟了吗
Wouldn't that have just made it worse?
好了 菲利普
Now, Philip,
用橄榄油按摩鸡胸和鸡腿
rub the breasts and thighs with olive oil.
好吧 虽然我没怎么试过
I'm a little new at this, but okay.
往火鸡里填料前
Before stuffing the bird,
最好取下首饰
you may want to remove your jewelry.
你是叫我摘掉婚戒吗
You mean take off my wedding ring?
你实在太坏了
You bad, bad girl.
你在跟谁说话
Who are you talking to?
我 没有 谁啊
I was -- nothing. Who?
我才不会舍弃二十年的
I'm not gonna throw away 20 years of --
沙拉是不是糊了
Is the salad burning?
东西都买好了
Here's everything,
包括你的所谓的蔓越莓酱
including your cranberry so-called sauce.
速度好快
That was fast.
我以每小时70英里的速度飞驶
I was driving 70 miles an hour.
好了 菲利普 在鸡胸和鸡腿上
Now, Philip, cover the breast and legs
包一层涂过黄油的干酪包布
with a buttered cheesecloth.
那声音有点诡异
That thing's a little creepy.
你才有点诡异
You're a little creepy.
我不喜欢
I don't love being the person
跟藏在摇篮里的备用火鸡躲在车库里
who hides in her garage with her secret crib turkey,
但做后备军本身就不是件有趣的事
but it's not always fun being the backstop.
你还说呢
You're telling me.
你每天下班回家之前
Until you get home from work every day,
我的主要工作就是让卢克好好活着
my main job is keeping Luke alive.
有次我发现他在跑步机上玩剪刀
I actually caught him on the treadmill with scissors.
你有没有嫉妒过他们
Do you ever feel jealous of them?
你也有过吗
You do, too?
是啊 没断过
Oh, yeah, all the time.
拜托 我们忙着收拾烂摊子的时候
Please, while you and I are busy being responsible,
一号痴线和二号痴线正玩得开心呢
thing one and thing two are off having so much fun.
拜托 价值十亿的点子
Ple-- "Billion-dollar ideas"?
这不是"真感觉挠头器"吗
The real head scratcher "T.M."
简直是经典
Now, that -- that is a classic.
还有这个
Look at this.
这是之前老爸用T恤喷射器给卢克改造的
Isn't that the old T-shirt cannon that dad modified for Luke
那个送报纸工具吗
to take on his paper route?
是啊 这主意很有趣 对吧
Yeah, it's a fun idea, huh?
其实 我们完全可以放松放松
You know, there's no reason you and I can't relax a little
像他们那样找点乐子
and have as much fun as they do.
赞成
I'm in.
我们也像他们一样犯犯傻
Let's be more like those idiots.
对 车库犯傻快乐
Yeah. Con-garage-ulations.
妥妥的
Nailed it.
你们在干什么
What's going on in here?
没什么 没什么
Um, n-nothing. Nothing.
我们 不是看上去的那样
We -- it's not what it looks like.
-真的 -真的
- Really? - No.
看上去好像
'Cause what it looks like
我掌勺后
is me taking over the cooking duties
我的姑娘们终于可以
has allowed my girls here
放放松 玩一玩了
to let down their hair and have fun for a change.
你们把这陈年旧货都挖出来了
Looks like you even dug out the old news-zooka.
哦不
Oh, no!
你不是吧 又来
Oh, my god! Again?!
那是意外
I-it was an accident!
一次才能说是意外 色狼
Once is an accident, perv.
宝贝 快点 该走了
Honey, come on. It's time to go.
来了
I'm ready.
不行 亲爱的
Oh, no, sweetie,
穿我们给你新买的那件漂亮感恩节裙子吧
We bought you that pretty new Thanksgiving dress.
可我想穿这身
But I want to wear this.
她想穿这件衣服 卡梅隆
She wants to wear that, Cameron.
你有什么想法
Thoughts?
莉莉 我们都盛装打扮
Well, Lily, uh, we're all dressed up.
你不希望表现得很失礼吧
You don't want to be disrespectful, do you?
我应该可以想穿什么就穿什么
I should be able to wear what I want.
好吧 亲爱的 听着
Okay, well, sweetie, listen,
你如果不穿那裙子我们恐怕就不能走了
I'm afraid we can't leave until you put that dress on.
好吧
Okay.
看到了吗
You see?
尽管你很想看到我大喊大叫
As much as you want me to yell,
可我有更有效的办法
I have a more effective method.
当你跟一个孩子说
When you say to a child,
"我会给予你礼遇和尊重"
"I will treat you with dignity and respect,"
那个孩子就会反过来对你说
that child will, in turn, say to you --
我没摘下标签 周一就把它退回去
I left the tag on. This is going back Monday.
就在你正酝酿盛气凌人的姿态时
Oh, and right in the middle of getting up
给你一个下马威
on such a high, high horse.
莉莉
Okay, Lily.
你说穿上就行的
You said put it on.
我穿上了 我们走吧
Well, it's on. Let's go.
我们不能让她这样自作主张
We cannot let her run the show like this.
好吧 相信我 我另有安排
Okay, trust me, I have another plan.
真的吗 因为现在
Really? Because right now,
我们的孩子就像越南版的安妮·霍尔
our child's walking around like a Vietnamese Annie Hall.
米奇尔 我会让她明白 她说得不算
Mitchell, I will make it clear that she is not the boss.
好吧 不不 我们现在不能出去
Okay, well, no, no, we can't go out now.
她从哪学来的这烦人的习惯
Okay, where did she learn that annoying habit?
克莱尔每周一都会去冥想班接她
Claire's been picking her up from meditation Mondays.
小火鸡就快美美地出炉了
The little bird's coming along nicely.
这可以成为我们新的感恩节传统
Hey, this could be our new Thanksgiving tradition.
什么传统 躲避我们的家人吗
What, hiding from our own family?
如果印第安人稍稍躲藏一点的话
Hey, if the Indians hid a little bit more,
他们现在可能还拥有自己的国家
they might still have this country.
不 只是远离大家 稍微清静一下
No, just taking a break from each other.
上帝知道我有多爱他们
God knows I couldn't love them more,
不过肯尼迪家族也不像我们这样频繁见面
but the Kennedys didn't get together as much as this family.
-所以你不觉得内疚吗 -内疚什么
- So you don't feel guilty? - For what?
没跟菲尔分享这瓶三十年的威士忌吗
Not sharing this 30-year-old scotch with Phil?
他用七喜对着喝 歌洛莉亚
He mixes it with 7up, Gloria.
那简直是仇恨罪
It's a hate crime.
希望这里没有停电
Let's hope the power isn't out here, too.
看起来没问题 门廊的灯亮着
It looks fine. The porch light's on.
火鸡来啦
Turkey coming through!
他们把该死的晚餐挪到这里来了
They moved the damn dinner here.
谢谢你帮我破解密码
Thank you for cracking the code.
把火鸡放到烤箱里 卢克
Pop the turkey in the oven, Luke.
损失了点时间 不过如果提高烤箱温度
Lost a little cooking time, but if we crank it to 550,
晚餐应该会按时做好
dinner should be on the table as scheduled.
遵命 主厨
Yes, chef.
这里进行得怎么样了
So, how's it going in here?
耽误了一点时间 不过现在恢复正常了
Minor little speed bump, but we're back on track.
你不用担心
You just relax.
亲爱的 我完全相信你
Honey, I trust you completely.
你有可爱的小助手
You've got your sweaty little helper,
妈妈我也有
and mama has hers.
谢谢
Thanks.
还有多久你才会偷溜回家
So, how long until you sneak home
把后备火鸡拿过来
and get the backup turkey?
有一点信心
Have a little faith.
你真的相信爸爸能做好吗
You're really trusting dad to do this?
对我有信心
In me.
火鸡在车后备箱里莉莉的背包中
It's in Lily's backpack in the trunk of the car.
这简直有病
This is crazy.
我们就下楼告诉他们我们在这里吧
Let's just go downstairs and tell them that we're here.
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
我们从墨西哥给他们发了视频
We sent them a video from Mexico.
我们当着他们的面撒谎
We lied to their faces.
你认为我们就这样下楼
You think we can just go downstairs
扔给他们点钱就能摆平这件事吗
and throw money at this and make it go away?
我在问你呢 这招行不行得通
I'm asking you. Do you think that would work?
我把包落在楼下了 曼尼知道
I left my purse down there, and Manny knows
我不带包绝对不会出门
that I would never leave town without it.
我的钱包和钥匙在吧台上
My wallet and keys are on the bar.
刚才抽的雪茄也在那里
And the cigar I was just smoking.
也许你说得对
Oh, maybe you're right.
大家快来 到外面照相
Come on, everybody! Outside for picture time!
我就知道你不可能是对的
I knew in my heart you couldn't be right.
我去拿杯威士忌
I'm gonna grab a scotch.
谁知道杰把七喜放在哪
Anyone know where Jay keeps the 7up?
好了
Okay.
菲尔 保持冷静
Phil, stay calm.
没错 路上的颠簸把砂锅菜毁了
Yes, the trip over here killed the casserole.
小面包也变硬了
The biscuits are hard.
肉汤上面的皮皱得就像佃农的脖子
The gravy has a skin on it like a sharecropper's neck.
你的洋葱都放进滚水里了吗 菲利普
Are your onions in hot water, Philip?
是的 我觉得我就在滚水里
Yes, I would say they are!
主厨 她只是想帮忙
Chef, she's just trying to help.
没错 还没结束呢
You're right. It's not over.
我们依然可以做出一顿丰盛的晚餐
We can still put a very nice meal...
我把插花忘在车里了
I left the centerpiece in the trunk.
会枯萎的
It's gonna get all wilted.
你要去哪
Where you going?
-一切进展得还顺利吗 -很好
- Everything okay in there? - Peachy.
我把插花忘在车里了
I left the centerpiece in the trunk.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我去弄点冰块
I was gonna go get some ice.
可以 我去帮你拿
Well, that's okay. I can go get it for you.
很好 我去帮你拿插花
Great. I can get your centerpiece.
我会把冰块放在那张桌子上的
I'll leave your ice right there on that table.
我也会把插花放在那里的
Which is where I will leave your centerpiece.
好吧
Okay, then.
不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
我想对之前发神经的事向你道歉
So, I want to apologize for flipping out before.
你当然不是色狼
Of course you're not a perv.
-过来 -不 没事的
- Come here. - No, it's okay.
-不 我不能 -来嘛
- No, I couldn't. - Come here.
没事的
It's okay.
那是什么
What is that?
-没什么 -别这样
- Oh, nothing. - No.
乍一看 挺像...
For a second, it looked like...
天啊
Oh, my God!
你拿了我的内裤
You have my underwear?!
不 好吧 是的
No. Okay, well, yes,
可不是你想的那样
but it's not what you're thinking.
它们本来在我的裤子里
Uh, they were in my pants.
你搞什么啊
What is wrong with you?!
我知道你迷恋我
I know you have a crush on me,
可这样也太痴汉了
but this is, like, deep freak!
不 我曾经迷恋过你
No, I used to have a crush on you,
不过现在不会了
but not anymore.
我就是运气不好
This is all just bad luck.
快拿着你的内裤走人吧
Just take your panties and go.
你们在重现当年的朝圣者
Re-creating the quaint part of the pilgrim story
拿内裤换玉米的诡异情节吗
where they trade underwear for corn?
天啊
Oh, my God.
这样也没那么糟嘛
This is not that terrible.
没错 我们喝着小酒
True. We have drinks.
乔在玩他的小玩具
Joe's playing with his "H."
大家都很开心
Everybody's happy.
干杯
Sí.
我们为啥要去我爸的卧室
And why are we going into my dad's bedroom?
开什么玩笑
You've got to be kidding me.
莉莉觉得自己想穿什么就可以穿什么
Lily thinks she can wear whatever she wants,
所以要是我们
so what if we --
不 不 我才不要穿
No, no, I am not putting on
我爸那些丑不拉几的休闲裤
one of my dad's hideous leisure suits.
没让你穿那个 放松
That is not the plan. Relax.
你还记得去年我们从克莱尔家的晚餐上
Do you remember last year when we picked her up
把她接回来的时候
from that family dinner at Claire's?
我们当时为胡娇的八十年代女士派对
We were dressed as Cagney and Lacey
穿成警花拍档的样子 她当时就翻脸了
for Pepper's '80s Ladies Party, and she flipped out.
你不是要穿歌洛莉亚的裙子吧
You're not putting on one of Gloria's dresses.
你就不能让我说完嘛
If you would simply just let me finish,
-计划不是那样的 -好吧 抱歉
- that is not the plan. - Okay, I'm sorry.
我们都要穿裙子
We're both putting on dresses.
不 我才不要这么做
No, I am not doing this.
米奇尔 就我一个人穿是没有效果的
Mitchell, it won't have any impact if I do it by myself.
我保证要是没有作用我们就按你说的做
I promise if it doesn't work, we'll do it your way.
这整个计划里我唯一喜欢的部分
You know, the only part of this I like
就是参观衣帽间
is getting to see this closet.
米尔奇 专心点
Mitchell, focus on the goal.
你知道她那么穿衣服
You know she only dresses the way
只是为了吸引眼球
she does to get attention.
几年前可能还挺可爱的
Maybe it was cute a few years ago,
可现在她已经老得不适合卖萌了
but she's just getting too old for this.
打她一顿屁股就好了
You know what she needs is a good spank on the bottom.
不行 这是你爸的方式
No, that's your father's way.
你是这么告诉他们的吗
You told them about that?
跟你说 要是我有这么个衣帽间
I'm telling you, if I had this closet,
我根本就不会出来[出柜]
I never would have come out.
你以后还可以再来
Well, you can come back later.
我们先把这事儿解决了
Let's just get this over with.
如果那两个贱姑娘有话想跟我说
If those mean girls have something to say to me,
他们就该当着我说
they should say it to my face.
一件事一件事慢慢来
One problem at a time.
你也听到了 他们还会回来
You heard them. They're coming back.
我们得离开这里
We've got to get out of here.
然后去哪里
And go where?
我们从后面的楼梯偷溜出去
We'll sneak down the back stairs.
再跑到前面的走廊去
We'll run around to the front porch
假装为了和大家团聚提前结束旅游回来了
and pretend we cut our trip short to be with everybody.
你赶快拿上外套和尿布
Now, you grab your coat, get the diaper bag.
我去拿几个行李箱 门口见
I'll grab a couple of suitcases, and I'll meet you there.
宝贝 你在读什么呢
Hey, sweetie, what are you reading?
你这穿的什么啊
What are you wearing?
我觉得是杜嘉班纳牌的
Well, I think it's Dolce & Gabbana.
她问你穿的是什么 不是牌子
She asked "What," not "Who."
你看到红地毯了吗
Do you see red carpet?
我们就在男生的衣服外面
Oh, well, we're just wearing dresses
套上裙子 跟你一样
over our boy clothes, like you.
不 我忘了
Oh, no, I forgot.
我们穿裙子你会不高兴 对吧
Us wearing dresses upsets you, doesn't it?
没错
Yeah, it does.
我们不想让你难受的
I don't want to make her uncomfortable,
可我们有权决定自己想穿什么
but we should be able to wear whatever we want.
怎么办 怎么办
what to do, what to do?
我不敢相信我居然穿得进歌洛莉亚的裙子
I just can't believe I slipped into one of Gloria's dresses.
别臭美了 那是件孕期斗篷
Relax. It's a maternity poncho.
好了 我们就说做了中午的航班回来
Okay, we tell them we took the noon flight out,
然后 乔呢
and, uh -- where's Joe?
我以为是你带他的
I thought you were bringing him!
我拉着两个箱子
I'm lugging two suitcases.
空箱子
Empty suitcases!
我们怎么能进去却没带着...
How are we gonna walk in there without...?
那只小火鸡
The little turkey!
我不喜欢你这么叫他
I don't like you calling him that.
不 我说的是我正在做的那个小火鸡
No, no, the little turkey I was cooking for us.
还在烤箱里呢
It's still in the oven.
好吧
Okay.
我就说我要送乔上楼睡觉
I'll say I have to put Joe down for a nap,
你负责处理掉火鸡
And you get rid of the turkey.
我只是说你很生气我忘了乔
I'm just saying you get very mad because I forgot Joe,
可是一提到火鸡...
but when it comes to turkey --
现在没时间说这个
I don't have time for thess.
如果莉莉看到了很不爽
No, if it really bothers Lily,
那我们就该改变了 小卡
then we should change, Cam,
这样莉莉可能也会考虑...
and then maybe Lily will also consider --
大家好啊
Hola, family!
我们想你们了 所以提前回来
We came back early because we miss you.
我们看见车停在外面
We saw the cars.
怎么了 你们把聚餐改在这里了吗
What, did you move the party here?
是啊 好久不见
Yes! Hello!
老爸 听着
So, hey, d-dad, listen,
我们之所以穿着这些裙子 是因为
the reason that we're wearing these dresses...
你们开心就好
Do what you got to do.
我现在得把这小家伙送上床
I got to get this little guy up to bed
他有点晕机
because that plane ride really knocked him out.
天哪
Oh, my God!
他没事的 你看他都没哭
He's fine. See? Not crying.
这可不一定是好兆头
That's not necessarily a good thing.
我要把行李拿到洗衣房去
And I'm gonna take the luggage to the laundry
因为墨西哥实在太脏了
because Mexico is very dirty.
爸和歌洛莉亚看见我们穿裙子
Dad and Gloria seem really okay
居然没有大惊小怪
with us wearing dresses.
是啊 我们又不是天天这样
Yeah, like we do it every day?
如果外公没意见 我也不介意
Well, if it's okay with grandpa, it's okay with me.
红莓酱好了
The cranberry sauce is okay,
肉汁也终于做好了
and the gravy is out of the woods.
由于你的心灵手巧
And, thanks to you,
那些小胡萝卜也应该没问题了
those baby carrots are gonna pull through.
它们还真是顽强
Well, they're fighters.
菲利普 最后一次
And now, Phillip, for the last time,
用油轻轻地刷一次大腿
lightly brush the thighs.
我会想念这个红色小抹布的
I'm gonna miss this randy little redcoat.
但我们还是要走到最后那一步
But it's time to cross the finish line.
不
No!
怎么了
What?!
我调高了烤箱温度 火鸡被烤缩水了
Cranking up the heat must have dried it up and shrunk it!
变得这么小了
It's tiny!
就这一只"鸽子"我怎么喂得饱11个人
How am I supposed to feed 11 people with this pigeon?!
老爸 火鸡做得怎么样了
Hey, dad, how's it coming?
很棒
Great!
再给我几分钟就可以上桌了
Just some last-minute touches, and we're good to go.
很好
Great.
他已经败走火鸡镇了
Panic in turkey town.
备用火鸡在莉莉的背包里
The backup turkey's in Lily's book bag.
把背包拿给我 我来搞定
Bring it to me. I'll do the rest.
从没觉得这么活力充沛过
I've never felt so alive.
我想再次跟你道歉
Hey, so, I want to try and apologize again.
没关系 都是我的错
It's okay. It was, it was all my fault.
这只是场意外而已
No, no, it was an accident.
-我们之间没问题 -谢谢
- We're good. - Thanks.
为了把事情一次性说清楚
And just to wrap things up once and for all,
当时大家都太激动了
some things were said in the heat of the moment
有些话不是真心的
that weren't really meant.
我知道你没把我当成变态
I know you don't think I'm a perv.
那个是不该说
Yes, that. That.
还有就是你说的
And, and also, that thing about
你不再暗恋我了
you not having a crush on me anymore.
我保证我没有
I-I promise I don't.
曼尼 得了吧
Oh, Manny, come on.
打开天窗说亮话
We're really trying to wrap things up.
我发誓 我现在都很少偷看你
I swear. I barely even look at you anymore.
这是从什么时候开始的
Well, when did that happen?
是从我把头发漂染之后吗
Was it when I lightened my hair?
浅色的头发让我黯然失色 对吗
It washes me out, right?
别人也这么觉得吗
Do other people feel this way?
海莉
Haley,
你是个美丽的女人 在你安定下来之前
you are a beautiful woman who will break many hearts
你会伤透很多人的心 包括我的
before you're done, mine among them.
你刚刚只是想"拥抱" 对吧
You meant "hug," didn't you?
真抱歉
I'm, I'm sorry.
我们需要一个小一点的盘子
We need a smaller platter or something
让这只火鸡看起来是正常大小
that makes this look normal-sized!
用杯垫怎么样
How do you feel about a coaster?
拿这个做三明治的火鸡片来充充数
Fill it in with this sandwich turkey.
我知道这已经过期了
It's past its sell-by date,
但我一直觉得保质期只是供参考而已
but I always think that's more of a suggestion, anyway.
我先去用面包把他们都喂饱
I'm gonna get them all loaded up on bread.
菲利普 接下来
And now, Philip,
你要怎么处理剩下的食材呢
what to do with all the leftovers.
我之前下载的那个甜心去哪了
What happened to the sweet girl I downloaded?
你跟女儿说清楚没有
So, did you have it out with our daughter?
要知道 今天是节日 我...
Well, you know, it's a holiday, and I...
好 那我来吧
Fine! I will handle this.
我就唱一辈子白脸好了
I will be the permanent bad guy in this family
就因为你太怕女儿会不喜欢你
cause you're so afraid of our daughter not liking you.
我就是想告诉你
But just so you know,
我的父母里 有一个想成为我的朋友
I had one parent growing up who wanted to be my friend
一个并不关心他是不是我的朋友
and another one who didn't care about that.
猜猜现在哪个还经常和我在一起
Guess which one is still in my life.
要来点美味的自制面包吗
Delicious homemade bread?
这就是普通的白面包啊
That looks like just regular white bread.
你们俩好像喝醉了 这能解酒
You two seem drunk. This will soak up the booze.
我喝醉了吗
Am I?
艾丽克斯 等等
Oh, Alex. Wait.
莉莉
Lily.
艾丽克斯把你的背包拿来给你了
Alex brought your backpack in for you.
你何不把它拿到我们的车上去呢
So why don't you go ahead and take it out to our car?
晚点再说吧
Maybe later.
莉莉 不行
No, Lily!
没关系的 我来吧
It's okay. I will take it now.
艾丽克斯 给我把包放下
Alex, put the backpack down!
老妈
Mom!
莉莉 衣着 早餐 还有其他事
Lily, you are not in charge of what you wear,
都不是你说了算
of breakfast, or anything.
现在 背上背包 朝着我们的车进发
Now, put that backpack on and march it out to the car!
这包太重了
It's too heavy.
生活是艰难的
Well, that's tough
因为以后我不会再帮你背着包了
because I'm not carrying it for you anymore!
我喜欢全新的你
I like this new guy, huh?
瞧吧 我就跟你们说太重了吧
See? I told you it was too heavy.
天啊 这包里到底装了什么啊
My gosh, what in the world is in this?!
不要
No!
克莱尔 我们落在你家的背包里
Claire, why is there a fully cooked turkey
怎么突然多了一只烤好的火鸡
in the backpack we left at your house?
是啊 克莱尔 怎么会出现的呢
Yes, Claire, why is there?
会不会是因为你烤了个备用的
Could it be you made a backup
因为你根本不相信我能做好这顿晚餐
because you never trusted me with the dinner at all?
我觉得有可能...
Well, I thought there was a chance that --
有可能我会搞砸一切吗
What, that I'd screw everything up?
你知道吗 我郑重告诉你
You know what? I have half a mind
我打算把我做的美味晚餐装好...
to pack up the beautiful meal I made --
晚餐上来啦
Dinner is served!
我 我不明白
I-I-I don't -- I don't understand.
是每个人都分到那样一盘吗
Does everybody get one?
我只是想着 万一你遇到麻烦
I was just going to sub in my turkey
我就献上我的火鸡 我的意思是...
if you got in trouble, which, I mean...
既然你已经碰了
Well, now you touched it,
那你就和艾丽克斯还有海莉分享那只吧
so you, Alex, and Haley will share that one.
黑肉献给你黑暗不信任别人的灵魂
Dark meat for your dark, untrusting soul.
菲尔
Phil!
话说这可是个崭新的背包
You know, this was a brand-new backpack,
现在里面却全都是烤火鸡的酱汁
and now it's got turkey juice all up in it!
行了 冷静点 大嗓门
Okay, back it up, old yeller.
好了 都少说两句吧
Okay, could we just stop?
天啊 这可是感恩节
This is Thanksgiving, for god's sake.
更别提明天还是卢克的生日呢
And not to mention that tomorrow is Luke's birthday.
对了 这个行李箱里有送给我的礼物吧
Hey, this is the suitcase with my present, right?
你们在视频里说了的
You had it in the video.
不要
No!
搞什么鬼
What the hell?!
恭喜你 卢克
Congratulations, Luke!
你终于长大成人了
You're finally a man!
在我的祖国 人们16岁生日时
In my country, when you turn 16,
会收到火鸡
you get your turkey.
等等 那段视频
Wait, you made the video
是你们在决定提早回来之前就拍摄好了的
before you decided to come back early.
你们难道打算把火鸡放里面4天吗
Were you gonna keep the turkey in there for four days?
那是种传统
It's a tradition.
你是怎么带着那玩意儿过海关的啊
How did you get that thing through customs?
那可是海关部门[风俗]
It is called customs.
他们 很尊重传统风俗
They...respect customs.
等等
Wait a minute.
我认识这只火鸡
I know this bird.
我给这对鸡胸上油一整天了
I've been oiling these breasts all day.
这是我的火鸡
This is my turkey!
烤得很完美
Done to perfection!
吃了吧 克莱尔
Eat it, Claire!
等等 爸爸的火鸡怎么会
Wait, so, how did dad's turkey
进他们的行李箱
get in their suitcase?
那个小火鸡又是从哪儿来的
And where did that small turkey come from?
你们怎么知道要回来这里的
And how did you know to come here?
晚餐本该是在克莱尔家举行的
Dinner was supposed to be at Claire's.
好了 好了
All right, all right.
乱得跟电影《凯恩号哗变》里的情节一样
It's like "The Caine Mutiny" In here!
我们的度假在最后时刻被取消了
Our vacation got canceled at the last minute.
我们决定对你们隐瞒这事
We decided not to say anything
因为我们想躲着清静一下
because we wanted a break.
躲着什么啊
A br-- a break from what?!
躲着感恩节的疯狂
From Thanksgiving craziness.
比如压力 吼叫
From -- from stress, from yelling,
以及这二位穿着裙子晃荡
from these two parading around in dresses.
-一次而已 -我们在家可不穿裙子
- That was a one-time thing. - Okay, we don't wear dresses at home.
听着 我知道感恩节
Now, look, I get that Thanksgiving
对于那些长年见不到的
is a big day for families
家人们来说是一件大事
who never see each other,
但我们这个家的人几乎时刻都黏在一起
but this group is together non-stop.
不如你们把行李箱里的这只火鸡带回家
Look, why don't you take the suitcase turkey home with you?
你们把备用火鸡带回家
You take the backpack turkey.
我们叫披萨外卖 今晚就到此为止吧
We'll order a pizza, and we'll all call it a night.
-好啊 是个好主意 -好吧 行
- Fine. That sounds great. - All right. Okay, fine.
不 不 不要
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
我知道我一般不会说这种话的
I know I seem like the last person to say this,
但我们不能直接略过感恩节啊
but we can't just skip Thanksgiving!
时光飞逝啊
Time is going by so fast.
似乎就在昨天 曼尼还对我一往情深
It seemed like only yesterday that Manny was hot for me,
现在却完全没有了
and he's not anymore.
某天 艾丽克斯也会有个男朋友
And someday, Alex may have a boyfriend
他会希望带她回他家去过感恩节
who wants her to spend it with his family.
好吧 那或许还需要等上几年
Okay, we probably got a little window there.
但我想说的是 我爱我疯狂的家人们
But my point is that I love my crazy family,
我想跟我的家人们一起过这个感恩节
and I want to spend this holiday with them.
如果你们想清静 我们可以略过圣诞节
If you want a break, we can skip Christmas.
-行吧 就这么定了 -好吧
- Fine. Settled. - Okay.
-那就略过圣诞节吧 -好吧 行
- Skip Christmas. - Okay. cool.
我早计划好和我的朋友们
I already had plans to spend Christmas
去卡波过圣诞节了
in cabo with my friends.
我必须想个办法脱身
I've got to get out of here.
我们为什么要把三只火鸡都吃掉啊
Why did we eat all three turkeys?
我希望明年的圣诞节是在周五
I hope that Thanksgiving's on a Friday next year,
那样我整个周末就可以一直睡了
so that I can sleep through the entire weekend.
妈 你能教化一下她吗 我实在累了
Mom, can you take this one? I'm exhausted.
你肯定是累坏了
Wow, you really must be.
菲尔 省省吧
Phil, give it up.
亲爱的 无论你怎么跳舞
Honey, you can dance all you want,
但你骗不了任何人
but you're not fooling anyone.
继续大力搅拌[鞭打]吧 菲利普
Continue to whip vigorously, Philip,
直到你的蛋白面糊[精液]变粘稠
until your meringue stiffens.
真好笑啊 我可没有...
That's hilarious. I don't --
面皮表层[屁股]变成漂亮的粉红色了吗
Are the cheeks turning nice and pink?
到底是出什么毛病了
What's the problem?
现在请置入冷水中
Now plunge into cold water.
我刚刚正打算建议你做同样的事呢
I was just about to suggest the same thing.